when the dress is dressing and the drink is drinking,
you know it's gonna be a good night.
If you've never tried craft mix,
it's a cocktail mix that's actually really, really good.
And if you're into your health like I am,
it's only 25 calories per packet, plus it's all natural.
They come in a whole bunch of really fun flavors.
My favorite is the mango marred,
but the strawberry mule is also absolutely delicious.
It's just a little sache, you add water and alcohol,
and you can even skip the water
if you just wanna taste any cocktail.
These have honestly saved me so much money,
and they're not full of sugar like cocktails at the barre.
So if you're interested, I'm gonna link them in the eye
because they're having a great deal right now,
but I don't know how much longer that's gonna last.